Your skin is freezing
Why don't you help me thaw it out?
with hellfire...
Trick or treat again
oh the fun will never end
on an endless halloween
la
la la
la la la
la la la la~
So come to me, and do my bidding
I'll make it worth your time
Bells all scream the doomsday chime
We'll bring christmas to an end!
Summon demons you can't
Summon demons you can't, com
Summon demons you can't, compre
Summon demons you can't, comprehend!
(oh how sublime)
Oh don't be scared,
you know that you can trust a friend like me
Steal all the candy!
Give everyone a fright!
Split the earth straight through the core
and bring a darkness that will
send
send you
send you all
send you all in
send you all insane
la
la la
la la la
la la la la~
Better hurry time is ticking
trust that it's a treat, not tricking
see your world as it's engulfed in flame
All part of my game!
Gonna take a piece of my world and
I'll bring it into yours
For just the price of your mind
to open countless doors
Oh don't be scared,
you know that you can trust a friend like me
Steal all the candy!
Give everyone a fright!
Come with me if you want never ending fear!
Follow me children...
Help
Help me
Help me bring
Help me bring the
Help me bring the end!